Can you see this, Mom?
We finally get to sing here.
Sakura, music has the power
to make people happy.
Okay!
The power to make people happy...
I wonder what Hayato-kun is doing right now.
Imitation Girl
Good morning. Kisaragi Hayato reporting in.
You said you had something to talk about?
Why are you dressed like that?
You don't understand, Kisaragi Hayato?
This is my summer house.
It's for rest and relaxation.
It makes complete sense
I'd be in a swimsuit.
Is it possible that
seeing me in my swimsuit is exciting you?
Th-That's not exactly...
Not used to dealing with women, are we?
Before we talk, how about I give you
a good look at me in my bikini
and make you blush even more?
P-President!
Don't, Claire-sama! I untied...
Huh?
Claire-sama!
Kisaragi Hayato!
You saw, didn't you?!
It was an accident!
I don't want your excuses!
I'm going to knock those memories of
Claire-sama's boobs out of your head—
Liddy?!
Damn that K-Kisaragi Hayato...
Where did he go?
What are you doing, Liddy?!
Kisaragi Hayato is right under—
Under?
What's going on here?
A-Anyway, let's get to the matter at hand.
We received a report from HQ yesterday.
It said that during the
Savage attack last month,
a variable stone was stolen from
the concert venue amid all that chaos.
A variable stone?
Kirishima Sakura was planning on
using it during her performance.
And they only reported it now...
I keep telling HQ to share all of their intel
with Little Garden, but they never listen.
A variable stone is an incredibly rare ore.
There's no guarantee that the thieves
won't come back looking for more.
We don't know who could be hiding where.
Kisaragi Hayato, make sure you
keep your eyes peeled.
We're counting on you to
guard Kirishima Sakura.
I understand.
I will make sure my mission
this afternoon is a success.
Excellent.
Now, on to private business.
Kisaragi Hayato,
I want a rematch.
We're having a swimming contest.
What?
Don't worry.
I've had a swimsuit prepared
for you, as well.
A... speedo...
This is going to be fun,
Kisaragi Hayato.
He's no fun, that Kisaragi Hayato.
Hi there, Hayato.
Emile...
Emilia.
We don't get to go out very often,
so let me be a normal girl on this date.
But what if any of our
fellow students see you?
It'll be fine.
We're pretty far from where
the Little Garden is harbored.
Anyway, what do you think?
Do you like it?
I... uh...
I-I think it's cute.
Thank you, Hayato.
I'm really happy.
Now, it's time for you to change.
Let's go. I've already picked out a store.
H-Hey.
Emil...
Emilia. Is this fine?
Oh. Yeah, it's great.
It looks really good on you.
You look cool.
I... I see.
What were you looking at?
I was thinking of getting
an accessory or something.
Plus it'd make for a good
memento of our date.
I think this'd work best.
But I like this one, too.
How about we get one?
On me.
What? Really?
Sure.
Yay! Thank you!
You like it?
Yeah.
This makes me yours, now.
Huh?
When a guy gives a girl a pendant,
it's a way of saying that
she is his, right?
N-No, I just...
I'll treasure this.
A-Anyway, how about we get going?
Th-This is bad.
Hide!
So Fritz, when did you get
your driver's license?
When you weren't paying attention, obviously.
Stop treating me like a kid!
Your head's always at
the most convenient height.
Stop it already!
That was scary.
Talk about bad luck.
I can't believe we came to the same store.
Actually, Fritz was the one who
told me about this place...
What?
I didn't think we'd run into him, though.
Oh, come on!
I didn't know any other stores,
and I wanted to at least go
on a girl-date with you once.
A-Anyway, we're going to
find an opening and leave.
It'll be all sorts of trouble if they see us.
Really?
I wouldn't mind staying like this
a little longer, though.
That was a close shave.
Sure was.
I'll go get us something to drink.
You wait here.
N-Nah, that's the guy's job.
It's fine.
An emergency call?
Kisaragi Hayato here.
Did something happen?
We have an emergency.
Don't tell me, Savage?
No, that's not it.
Kirishima Sakura has disappeared
from her hotel room.
Though it seems that she wasn't kidnapped,
but rather left of her own free will.
It looks like she turned off
the GPS on her PDA, as well.
But where would she go?
That's what we're trying to find out.
Depending on how it goes,
we may have you join the search.
Actually, I'd rather have you
join in now, but...
President... Is it just me,
or do you sound angry?
What are you saying, Kisaragi Hayato?
Why would I be angry that you went shopping
with Emile Crossfode while I'm working here?
Uh... I'm sorry...
You coldly turned down
my challenge this morning, too.
Instead of apologizing, make it up to me
by going shopping with me next time.
S-Sure, I don't mind.
Really?!
A-Anyway, contact me if you learn anything.
Understood?
I wonder where Sakura went...
Right here.
Huh?
Sakura?
What are you doing here?
Everyone's looking for you.
I came to see you.
That looks pretty good on you.
Th-Thank you.
Never mind that!
How did you know where I was?
You don't know?
Just in case something happens,
a client can track their
bodyguard through GPS.
Come. We don't have much time.
There's a place I want to go with you.
With me?
Where?
Secret spot.
But I guarantee it's a wonderful place.
Now, let's go.
H-Hold on a second.
What?
You have something to do?
N-No...
If she runs into Emilia,
things are going to get ugly...
Fine. I'll go with you.
But in exchange, I want you
to contact Souffle-san.
That's my condition.
Sure. Got it.
Now, let's go, Mr. Hero
of these Zwei Islands.
Could you get us a taxi?
Yeesh.
Sorry, Emilia.
I'll contact you later.
I'm back, Hayato!
Huh?
Hayato?
A text?
Wait...
Wh-What should I do?
Yes. That's right.
I texted Emilia about what happened,
but I'm sure she's gonna be mad at me.
Look, I'm sorry I left
without saying anything.
Yes.
I've more or less finished the song
that's going on the album, so don't worry.
Don't worry?
Hayato-kun, you explain the rest.
Hello, Sakura? Are you listening?
What?!
Sorry, Souffle-san.
It's Kisaragi Hayato...
We're the ones who should
be sorry, Kisaragi-san.
You're having to deal with
Sakura's whims and fancies.
No, it's fine.
Just doing my job.
What the heck? You're no fun.
Yes, yes.
I'll contact you about that.
Thank you.
She wants us back by
rehearsal, no matter what.
I know that.
Anyway, it's fine.
Now no one is going to bug us.
So where are we going?
You think you can tell me now?
I told you it was secret.
Did we find Kirishima Sakura?
Yes.
Kisaragi Hayato just informed us
that she's with him currently.
According to her PDA's location info,
they're heading towards
the island's Grand Canyon.
Good grief.
What a boob.
Look, Hayato-kun.
Isn't it an amazing view?
Yeah.
That's awesome.
It's the Zwei Grand Canyon.
I really wanted to show you this.
Why me?
You're the hero who protected this vista...
This precious place my mom showed me.
Sakura...
I'm sorry.
When I met you yesterday,
all I could think of was how you protected this place
and preserved my memories with mom...
...and I got kind of excited.
I was acting pretty weird, huh?
Yeah.
Hayato-kun, I want to thank you again.
Thank you for saving
something so special to me.
Hey, stop it. I just fought without
really thinking about anything.
I couldn't have won without
the help of the other Slayers.
You're still a hero to me.
So let me thank you.
Sure.
That's a good song.
My little sister used to hum that.
That couldn't be.
My mom created that song for me.
I've rarely ever let anyone hear it.
Even now, I only hummed it because
I wanted you to hear it.
Hayato-kun, could you
tell me your sister's name?
It's Karen...
Were you in Gudenberg during
the second Savage attack?
Huh?
In the shelter downtown?
Y-Yeah...
Could you be...
Back then, when I'd lost my mother and was all alone,
this sibling pair told me they liked my singing.
The sister's name was Karen.
I didn't get to hear the brother's name.
So it was you, Hayato-kun...
I sang the song my mom composed for me.
And in the end, the brother said to me...
I don't know much about music,
but your singing makes me feel better.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe that boy—
the one who changed my entire life—
was you, Hayato-kun.
Your life?
Yes...
When you praised me back then,
I started to like singing.
It filled me with confidence.
And that's what made me
want to become a singer.
I never thought we'd meet like this.
I'm so happy I kept singing.
But we only met that one time, right?
You were gone the next day.
Yes. My father, who I had never
met before, came to get me.
Shortly after I was taken back to
my father's homeland,
I became ill with an unknown virus.
The same as Karen...
Souffle was a genetic engineer
who was in charge of me at first.
But I didn't get better at all.
Instead, I lost my voice,
and wasn't able to sing anymore.
My father, without asking Souffle at all,
sold me off to a Warslarn research facility.
There we were injected with a vaccine
made from Savage fluids,
under orders from the director
of the lab, Vitaly Tynyanov.
Several children died because
the vaccine was so potent.
But I survived and came to
be able to sing once more.
I was saved by Vitaly's vaccine.
However, the vaccine continued to be
injected into the children that survived.
What do you mean?
Vitaly's goal isn't to cure illness.
It was to artificially turn
normal humans into Slayers.
Even when we were able to deploy a Hundred,
they continued to inject the vaccine,
attempting to give us even stronger powers.
No matter what the side effects,
they kept doing it.
Latuni!
Sing, Sakura.
Sure.
And I sang.
Because everyone calmed down when I did.
So they could feel a little bit more at ease.
Over and over again.
But not one of them
made a complete recovery.
Sakura!
By luck, I survived.
My illness was cured,
and while I can't fight,
I am now a Slayer.
I can even sing,
and be Kirishima Sakura, the diva.
But I...
So you're a Variant, too.
Hayato-kun, why do you know about Variants?!
Oh...
And you said "too."
What do you mean by that?
Uh...
Well, I'm a Variant, too.
You, too?
Yeah.
I only became one by accident, though.
Also, I only recently learned about it.
I see...
You're the same as me...
Wow!
That's great, Hayato-kun!
Sakura?
I mean, isn't it amazing?
You're the person who changed my life,
the hero who preserved my memories here,
and a Variant who shares the same fate as me!
And we just happened to meet again
and spend time together?
This has to be a miracle!
Calm down.
I just thought of a bunch of songs!
I can't sit here.
I'm going to go the concert hall and work
on writing songs between rehearsals!
Hey, Sakura, wait!
Hayato-kun, hurry up!
Yeah, I'm coming!
It's good they had a bus.
I didn't think there
wouldn't be any taxis around.
There weren't many tourists there.
Good.
It's a special place for my mom and me.
I wouldn't want a lot of people there.
I guess.
But I...
Hayato-kun, do you have a moment?
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Wh-What? What happened?
I don't know.
A Savage?!
This is bad!
Everyone get down!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
The Diva's  Love Song